this is how to have a tantric orgasm all
by yourself
all you have to do is think about
somebody bring them into your being into
your energy field
and let the rest take care of itself
i'll show you how it's done
you had me at all by yourself you
shirtless canadian
now let's learn how to feverishly
meditate in this week's breakdown
master the mind job and you'll cut your
lube budget in half
wranglers are an odd choice but the
u-fit crotch will make a great splooge
receptacle
i'd rather just take yoga classes until
i can blow myself
i'm this far not only does it feel great
this is also a discreet way to kill time
during the slow parts of church
hey since your hands are free why not
play with your b-cups
if i could ejaculate without using my
hands i would eat buffalo wings
right because they're so delicious yet
so messy
turning kind of red looks like his whole
body is ashamed of what's about to
happen
all right he's either fighting off a big
sneeze or his energy field is being
plowed by a sexy ghost
all right wrap it up the family waiting
to get their easter portrait taken is a
little freaked out
you know what also feels pretty great
during sex another person
and there you have it under one minute
seems like a good way to gunk up your
zipper
i'm just glad he doesn't feel the need
to prove it and for that we thank you
all right may zeus honor us with
something next
[Music]
still not as weird as a pool party at
brian singer's house
shame on you brian for scaring these
boys for life
with your crappy superhero remakes
now let's find out how centaurs are made
in this week's breakdown these
telenovelas are getting goddamn
ridiculous
what a sexy equestrian the scenery the
spanish narration
it's all very romantic this may be the
most beautiful video i've ever seen
come on at least i know it's not peyton
manning getting limber in the off season
that's a horse doing yoga
that philly really wants a great ass she
should do horse pilates
all the exercise in the world won't help
that face
don't forget to point your hooves beet's
getting whipped for three miles at the
kentucky derby
my yoga instructor almost never kisses
me
just dip your junk in salt already
i'd like to place a ten dollar exacta
that the jockey finishes first
and they're off just screwing the
stables
that's how he became the horse fister
and before three of you tell me you
already saw this video on at midnight
know that i found out about it after it
was too late to make a change
maybe i should watch the show more i do
i like to play along at home
as soon as anyone yells points i turn
off my tv
and for that we say namaste
you